[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "rust?",
    "answer": "fedge",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-20T15:44:14.185Z",
    "category": "FIRST"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "amk",
    "answer": "dina",
    "tag": "pap",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-22T20:35:24.537Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "votreQuestion",
    "answer": "votreReponse",
    "tag": "votreTag",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-23T14:17:47.737Z",
    "category": "FIRST"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "1+1+1",
    "answer": "3",
    "tag": "mathimatik",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-22T00:17:44.160Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "A practice to work in pair on same computer.",
    "tag": "Teamwork",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-22T20:25:04.121Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "rist.",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-20T14:38:45.749Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "question?",
    "answer": "réponse",
    "tag": "tagtag",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-22T22:56:53.145Z",
    "category": "SECOND"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is pair programming ?",
    "answer": "rist.",
    "tag": "rust",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-24T09:16:17.111Z",
    "category": "FIRST"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "question?",
    "answer": "réponse",
    "tag": "CARTE DE TEST",
    "lastDateRevised": "2024-02-24T09:38:34.284Z",
    "category": "FIRST"
  },
    {"id":10,"question":"badis","answer":"tighlit","tag":"tag","lastDateRevised":"2024-02-24T10:33:38.795Z","category":"FIRST"},
    {"id":11,"question":"comment","answer":"il va","tag":"tagat","lastDateRevised":"2024-02-24T10:35:52.704Z","category":"FIRST"}
]